<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Ashb0rn-Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Ashb0rn-Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my Blog!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;welcome-to-my-blog&#34;&gt;Welcome to my blog&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hello everyone and welcome to my blog, I know the name is long but you can call me Ashb0rn for now. Before I get going, I did get the name from Solo Leveling, I wanted it to be Ashb0rn like what I go by but this will do for now since it is &lt;em&gt;technically&lt;/em&gt; his title. For reference and image of Ashborn is below.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Solo_Leveling_manhaw_Ashborn_on_horse1.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;whoami&#34;&gt;Whoami&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I guess I need to start off with this. For the time being I want to keep my actual name as private as possible. I know that maybe one day it will get out there but since I am trying to start a career in CyberSecurity I want to keep that part as quiet as possible. I can give away a few basics however.&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I graduated with my Bachelors degree and majored in CyberSecurity.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I am a huge anime/manga nerd, I have a collection that I am constantly building and I want to keep expanding it. Currently my favorite anime/manga would be between Jujutsu Kaisen, Solo Leveling (obviously) and FireForce. However I am currently watching Season 2 of Solo Leveling, Soul Eater and FairyTail.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I have been into computers since I was 12 and I built my first one when I was 13. I will never forget that Christmas morning when I did get all the parts and when I got to build it. After that it was a rabbit hole of gaming, programming and later on cybersecurity.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Since I mentioned gaming above I am avid gamer and my favorite type of games are FPS games. I have two story driven FPS games I love and that is the &lt;em&gt;DOOM&lt;/em&gt; franchise and the &lt;em&gt;Bioshock&lt;/em&gt; franchise. I basically grew up playing &lt;em&gt;Counter Strike: Global Offensive&lt;/em&gt; and so I have a love for tactical shooters but I will really play and first person shooter I can get my hands on. I will also play MMORPG&amp;rsquo;s from time to time but I haven&amp;rsquo;t really find the right one for me yet.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s really all I can think of for now but check back from time to time to see what games I am currently playing or Anime I am watching.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;cybersecurity&#34;&gt;CyberSecurity&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;With the mention of this so much above you had to know it was going to get its own section right? I started really getting into this when I was in college. I knew of it thanks to the &lt;em&gt;Snowden&lt;/em&gt; movie and the &lt;em&gt;Mr.Robot&lt;/em&gt; T.V. show but I never really did anything major. Like any other first time &amp;lsquo;hacker&amp;rsquo; I downloaded Kali Linux and took on the Elliot persona until I realized I was not a hacker in the slightest and I wasn&amp;rsquo;t even a script kiddie at this point. Back to the college route however, I took some coding classes (including the dreaded &lt;em&gt;Data Structures and Algorithms&lt;/em&gt;) as well as some digital forensics classes which got my foot in the door with a deeper understanding of computers in general. It was in my very first digital forensics class however I knew for a fact I wanted to go down the cybersecurity rabbit hole and so I did.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I took a major interest in Red teaming with &lt;strong&gt;ZERO&lt;/strong&gt; background information on networking or any of the basics (as one does) and realized I knew so little about anything and after maybe 3 days of struggling on TryHackMe and looking up every single write up for everything I was doing, I decided to go learn my basics. I learned via TryHackMe as well as my classes. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until my digital forensics 2 class I got to do some proper &amp;lsquo;hacking&amp;rsquo; however.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;As time went on I grew my skills and understood more and with time I was able to start breaking more ground on that pesky red team module on TryHackMe. After learning so much I decided to ask for extra projects from professors (got to do some fun penetration tests) as well as join my college&amp;rsquo;s cybersecurity club where I competed in &lt;em&gt;HiveStorm&lt;/em&gt; as well as &lt;em&gt;CCDC&lt;/em&gt;. Both competitions were very tough but also informative as I got to gauge my skill with my peers as well as learn from the mistakes I made during the competitions (I learned a lot from these competitions since as a team we made many, many, &lt;strong&gt;MANY&lt;/strong&gt; mistakes).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now I spend most of my free time with my friends and working on HackTheBox machines or working on my Home Lab which is the main reason I wanted to make this blog. I wanted somewhere to store my write-up&amp;rsquo;s and documentation for my homelab as well as a place for others to maybe learn something new from me.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s basically it for now. I am constantly working on something new or learning something so I will be doing my best to keep this as up to date as possible. Please enjoy your stay on the blog and if you learn something new, consider bookmarking my blog to come back to one day.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
